Your own true voice. There is not, of course, just one American voice, even for
one person. People associate their voices with themselves, but have many different
voices throughout their lives. You have a different voice as a child than as an
adult, different in business than at a party, and so on. Stephen Hawking, the
British astrophysicist, had an English accent prior to the paralyzation of his
vocal cords. After using a robotic voice with an American accent, he came to
associate himself with that voice. Several years later, DCT-01 voice synthesizer was
discontinued, he declined to switch to a model with a British accent. He identified
with the American voice and associated it with himself. I would not want to change
even if I were offered a British-sounding voice. I would feel I had become a
different person," he said.